// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is a digital service that enables collaboration between two or more different but interdependent groups of users who interact through the internet?",
    answer: "c. Online Platform",
    options: [
      "a. Word Processor",
      "b. World Wide Web",
      "c. Online Platform",
      "d. ICT Content Development"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following online creation tools will be used if a person wants to create a video presentation?",
    answer: "c. Powtoon",
    options: [
      "a. Piktochart",
      "b. Prezi",
      "c. Powtoon",
      "d. Zamzar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What type of online platform is Facebook?",
    answer: "c. Social Media",
    options: [
      "a. Web Page Creation",
      "b. Cloud Computing",
      "c. Social Media",
      "d. Dating App"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a presentation/visualization platform?",
    answer: "d. Prezi",
    options: [
      "a. Google Drive",
      "b. Wikimapia",
      "c. Zamzar",
      "d. Prezi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which online application will allow the user to publish, edit, manipulate, organize, and delete web content?",
    answer: "c. Content Management System",
    options: [
      "a. Rage Comic Generator",
      "b. Microsoft Office 365",
      "c. Content Management System",
      "d. Youtube Video Editor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following platforms can be used for online community connections and networking?",
    answer: "c. Twitter",
    options: [
      "a. Dropbox",
      "b. Evernote",
      "c. Twitter",
      "d. Weebly"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which type of online platform will you use if you want to back up your file in your computer to the online storage?",
    answer: "a. Cloud Computing",
    options: [
      "a. Cloud Computing",
      "b. File Management",
      "c. Mapping",
      "d. Social Media"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a purpose of online platforms and applications?",
    answer: "a. repairing computers",
    options: [
      "a. repairing computers",
      "b. sharing information",
      "c. organizing files",
      "d. market place"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not true about online creation tools and applications?",
    answer: "c. They are a combination of different technologies that are set in one place.",
    options: [
      "a. They perform specific tasks.",
      "b. They do not require installation on computers.",
      "c. They are a combination of different technologies that are set in one place.",
      "d. They can be accessed anytime and anywhere if the user is connected to the internet."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is the best platform to use if you want to advertise your clothing line business?",
    answer: "a. Social Media",
    options: [
      "a. Social Media",
      "b. Mapping",
      "c. File Management",
      "d. Presentation/ Visualization"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "If you wanted to share your travel, food, and cultural experiences in different places, which online platform will you use?",
    answer: "d. Webpage Creation",
    options: [
      "a. Cloud Computing",
      "b. Mapping",
      "c. File Management",
      "d. Webpage Creation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following is the least priority in choosing online creation tools, platforms, and applications for ICT development?",
    answer: "d. Security",
    options: [
      "a. Affordability",
      "b. Browser Support",
      "c. Collaborative Features",
      "d. Security"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which situation will be best addressed by mapping platforms?",
    answer: "d. Aldrin wanted his gym’s location to be easier to find by his potential clients.",
    options: [
      "a. Grace wanted to connect to her distant relatives in the province.",
      "b. Ramon’s boss asks him to create a jingle for their new bread product.",
      "c. Dona will have to present a business proposal next week for her client.",
      "d. Aldrin wanted his gym’s location to be easier to find by his potential clients."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which situation is not suitable if a person will use audio and visual content tools and applications?",
    answer: "c. Surveying people about their preference in visual arts.",
    options: [
      "a. Editing videos for instructional Zumba.",
      "b. Mixing music for the cultural dance presentation.",
      "c. Surveying people about their preference in visual arts.",
      "d. Creating infographics about the importance of wearing face masks."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT true about online platforms?",
    answer: "c. Online platforms are fixed and cannot be modified.",
    options: [
      "a. Online platforms can be a marketplace.",
      "b. Online platforms are run by several applications.",
      "c. Online platforms are fixed and cannot be modified.",
      "d. Online platforms interact between two or more users."
    ]
  },
];
